kuro5hin.org 2002-12-03

# kuro5hin.org || Our Privacy Policy

| ****Our Privacy Policy****  
---  
   
**Kuro5hin.org Privacy Notice**  
Effective **06/13/2000** , and retroactively to all accounts created before that date.

**Privacy Notice Table Of Contents:**
    Our Commitment To Privacy
    The Information We Collect
    How We Use Information
    Our Commitment To Data Security
    Our Commitment To Children's Privacy
    How To Access Or Correct Your Information
    How To Contact Us
 **Our Commitment To Privacy**

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested. 

**The Information We Collect:**

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the Kuro5hin.org website. You can sign up for a user account here. The only personal information collected upon signing up for an account is a working email address. 

**The Way We Use Information:**

We use your email address only to send a confirmation email when you sign up for an account and to allow you to reset your password if you lose or forget your old one. We also send you an automated notice if a story you submit is accepted or declined. No other use is now or ever will be made of this address, although the administrators may personally email you if extenuating circumstances arise where this is required. We will not send you any other email unless you contact us first and specifically request information, technical help, or editorial assistance. We do not sell this address, or link it to any other personal information. 

Optionally, you may also provide a "fake" email address, which may be munged in any way you like to avoid automated web-roving spam-bots, a website URL, a PGP/GPG private key, and a short biographical blurb. You are not required to provide any of these things, and no use will ever be made of them by Kuro5hin.org besides diplaying them with your posted comments and on your user info page. 

You may also, after signing up, change your real email address to an invalid one. If you do this, you are giving up any ability to automatically reset your password. If you feel it is important though, you are welcome to do so. 

**Our Commitment To Data Security**

To prevent unauthorized access, to maintain data accuracy, and to ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. 

**Our Commitment To Children's Privacy:**

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13. 

**How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information**

You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by logging in, and clicking the "User Preferences" link in the box on the right-hand side of every page. If you are logged in right now, then clicking [this link](http://www.kuro5hin.org/?op=user&tool=prefs) will take you to your edit page. 

To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections, by requiring you to enter your current password before changing any of your user information. 

**How To Contact Us**

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please send us an email at [help@kuro5hin.org](mailto:help@kuro5hin.org).
